ubsApp.quizConfig = {
    "quizQ1":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":1,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "We should keep our savings with banks because: ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"4",
				"optionName":"q1",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q1",
						"optionValue": "It is safe",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 4
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q1",
						"optionValue": "Earns Interest",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q1",
						"optionValue": "Can be withdrawn anytime",
						"id":3,
						"priority":2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q1",
						"optionValue": "Can be withdrawn anytime",
						"id":4,
						"priority":1
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
	"quizQ2":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":2,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "Bank does not give loan against: ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"3",
				"optionName":"q2",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q2",
						"optionValue": "Gold Ornaments",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q2",
						"optionValue": "LIC Policy",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q2",
						"optionValue": "Lottery Ticket",
						"id":3,
						"priority":1
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q2",
						"optionValue": "NSC",
						"id":4,
						"priority":4
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
	"quizQ3":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":3,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "100/- Rupee note is signed by: ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"3",
				"optionName":"q3",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q3",
						"optionValue": "Prime minister",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q3",
						"optionValue": "Finance minister",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q3",
						"optionValue": "RBI Governor",
						"id":3,
						"priority":1
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q3",
						"optionValue": "None Of the above",
						"id":4,
						"priority":4
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
	"quizQ4":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":4,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "ATM password should be kept in: ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"3",
				"optionName":"q4",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q4",
						"optionValue": "Personal Diary",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q4",
						"optionValue": "Office Diary",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q4",
						"optionValue": "Memory",
						"id":3,
						"priority":1
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q4",
						"optionValue": "All of the above",
						"id":4,
						"priority":4
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
	"quizQ5":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":5,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "ATM password to be shared only with: ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"4",
				"optionName": "q5",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q5",
						"optionValue": "Spouse",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q5",
						"optionValue": "Obedient son",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q5",
						"optionValue": "Obdient daughter",
						"id":3,
						"priority":4
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q5",
						"optionValue": "None of the above",
						"id":4,
						"priority":1
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
    "quizQ6":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":1,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "Nomination can be done in: ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"4",
				"optionName":"q6",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q6",
						"optionValue": "Savings Bank Account",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 4
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q6",
						"optionValue": "Recurring Deposit account",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q6",
						"optionValue": "Fixed Deposit account",
						"id":3,
						"priority":2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q6",
						"optionValue": "All of the above",
						"id":4,
						"priority":1
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
    "quizQ7":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":1,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "Minimum age required to open SB account in the bank  ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"2",
				"optionName":"q7",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q7",
						"optionValue": "8 years",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q7",
						"optionValue": "10 years",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 1
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q7",
						"optionValue": "12 years",
						"id":3,
						"priority":2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q7",
						"optionValue": "None of the above",
						"id":4,
						"priority":4
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
    "quizQ8":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":1,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "Bank does not provide loans for ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"4",
				"optionName":"q8",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q8",
						"optionValue": "Crop loans",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q8",
						"optionValue": "Education loans",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 4
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q8",
						"optionValue": "Home loans",
						"id":3,
						"priority":2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q8",
						"optionValue": "Drinking and Gambling",
						"id":4,
						"priority":1
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
    "quizQ9":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":1,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "KYC means ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"1",
				"optionName":"q9",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q9",
						"optionValue": "Know your Custome",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 1
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q9",
						"optionValue": "Know your character",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 4
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q9",
						"optionValue": "Both of the above",
						"id":3,
						"priority":2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q9",
						"optionValue": "None of the above",
						"id":4,
						"priority":3
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
    "quizQ10":{
		"category":"Quiz",
		"repeatforuser":false,
		"repeatforall":true,
		"questionTime":3000,
		"displayCalculator":true,
		"minimumInventoryScoreRequired":"0",
		"inventoryScoreToBeChanged":"0",
	 	"templates":[
	 		{
				"templateId": 1,
				"questionId":1,
				"templateType": "quiz",
				"noOfQuestions":"",
				"question": "Loans from Money Lenders are: ",
				"questionTime":3000,
				"optionsTime":2000,
				"questionHeading":"GST",
				"helpPageName":"quizHelp",
				"credit":{
					"inventory":0,
					"bankBalance":0,
					"reputationPoints":1,
					"cash":0,
				},
				"answer":"4",
				"optionName":"q10",
				"options": [
				    {
						"optionName":"q10",
						"optionValue": "With High Rate Of Interest",
						"id":1,
						"priority": 3
					},
					{
						"optionName": "q10",
						"optionValue": "No proper accounting",
						"id":2,
						"priority": 4
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q10",
						"optionValue": "No transparency",
						"id":3,
						"priority":2
					},
					{
						"optionName":"q10",
						"optionValue": "All of the above",
						"id":4,
						"priority":1
					}
				],
				"onClickPage": {
					"nextPage" : "",
					"hideScenarios" : false
				}
			}
		]
	},
}